FULL STACK DEVELOPER

JOHN LEE

CONTACT



codebeast0420@gmail.com



skype:live:.cid.e6bc6f99f1039ac1



273B New Bridge Road, Chinatown Singapore

EXPERTISE SKILLS

HTML, CSS, JS, PHP

REACT, VUE, REACT NATIVE

NODE, LARAVEL, CI

MYSQL, MONGODB

ABOUT ME

Full stack developer and blockchain engineer with over 7 years of experience coding websites and NFT. Proficient with Java/JS, Angular, Vue, React, Python, Django, Smart contract, NFT.

Proficient with Cyber security, IT risk management and HR methodology.

WORK EXPERIENCE

HCL Singapore Pte Ltd 01/2021 - 02/2022

SENIOR FULL STACK DEVELOPER &

BLOCKCHAIN ENGINEER

HCL is an international Technology and Management Consulting

Group with a rapid pace development and innovative solutions for demanding projects. I worked as a full-stack developer and blockchain engineer here,

Developed 40 responsive modern websites for clients in a variety of Developed 3 NFT games

Developed architecture using SQL procedures and triggers for 10 different applications

Worked with Core Java to develop automated solutions to include web interfaces using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Web services

PALO IT Singapore 08/2019 - 01/2021

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

PALO is a services company that provides customers with access to products, insights and experience that enrich lives and build business success.

Back-end development with PHP Frameworks
Developed 10+Micorservices using Serverless
Introduced TypeScript to the developer community
Implemented continuous delivery using 100% declarative infrastructure and automated deployment

LANGUAGE SKILLS

ENGLISH

CHINESE

Software AG (Singapore) Pte Ltd 05/2017 - 07/2019

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Software AG is a leading Digital Product Studio in Singapore, helping companies to thrive on mobile apps, the web, VR/AR and IoT.

Worked with an agile team of 12 members and provided end to end solutions for clients

Developed my team-work skills by working in close collaboration with 6 other students.

Built a custom dashboard that reduces support tickets by 50%

Had the responsibility to train 4 people the front-end basics and helped them develop further

Designed and Developed UI design for over 15 clients using CSS, HTML, Vue and React; websites scoring over 85 on Lighthouse

Syntax Company 05/2015 - 01/2017

Team Leader& Project Manager

Syntax Company

Syntax is a universal digital loyalty program that offers unique and fun rewards at the places you love.

Managing a12-person team

Simultaneously created & maintained scheduled jobs in SQL Server for space maintenance and daily backups of system and user databases for 10 clients

Managed 6 outsourced web developers, designers and content writers Increased company revenue by 30% within 2 months after developing and implementing business logic for over 20 features

EDUCATION

2010 - 2014

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER SCIENCE

National University of Singapore